JORDAN O'GRADY

jord_ogrady@hotmail.com · 0452 399 848 · Engadine GitHub - https://github.com/JordanNotAvailable

I am a creative, hardworking problem solver with broad industry experience in construction, sales and business. I've found my passion studying full-stack web development and I am excited for the direction that I am pivoting to in tech and am motivated to learn what I can. Any questions please feel free to reach out to any of my contact details within the header.

EXPERIENCE

OCTOBER 2022 - CURRENT

STUDENT, **SOFTWARE DEVELOPMENT**

- Studying Full-Stack Software Development part time at Sydney university Monday, Tuesday, and Thursday from 6pm-10pm with a project every week for a total of 25 including 3 group projects.
- Languages I've learned to use so far are HTML, CSS, JavaScript, SQL, Sequelize, ejs and handlebars as well as using a variety of libraries such as socket.io, nodemon, express, dotenv, bycrypt and lint.
- Tools used are MongoDB, Compass, MySQL, Workbench, Heroku, Bash, GitHub, GitLab, Gist and Projects.
- JavaScript is my main language.
- I'm forever learning new things and am very excited to pick up new tricks and different languages as I further develop my skills.

JANUARY 2021 – NOVEMBER 2022 FOUNDER, APPLIED JOBS

- APPLIED JOBS is a start-up I started in early 2021 after completing my Business Operations cert 3 and is a job seek and advertising platform like seek or indeed but only showing the user jobs they can apply for and businesses users that are qualified for the role.
- Key roles within this were market research, accounting, management, admin, marketing and sales.
- 30% success rate on converting cold calls to warm gathering 5 points of information for most.
- I paused the pursuit of this business to further develop my skills in other areas such as tech.

APRIL 2021 – JUNE 2021

SALES AGENT, INSIGHT

- Over the phone salesman doing cold calls for different charities.
- Averaging 600 calls a day and 4 sales with a high of 1246 calls in one day.
- Highest sale of \$300 from a \$10 talk up.

MARCH 2018 - MARCH 2020

LABOURING, MULTIPLE BUSINESSES

- Working in multiple businesses in different industries including events, scaffolding and sign writing/installation.
- Covid was the impetus for me diversifying my skillset and taking a career change and enjoying my current path of full-stack web development.

EDUCATION

2022 - CURRENT

Full-stack web development bootcamp, Sydney University

2021

Certificate 3 in Micro Business Operations, MTC

2017

Year 10 ROSA, Endeavour High School

2017

White Card

SKILLS

- Fast learner
- Hardworking
- Innovative
- Reliable
- Business development
- Technical troubleshooting
- Preparation
- Computer hardware

Languages

- JavaScript
- HTML
- CSS
- SQL and Sequelize

Tools

- MySql
- Workbench
- GitHub
- GitLab
- Gist
- Projects
- Bash
- Insomnia
- MongoDB
- Compass
- Visual Code